<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AHL</string>
    <string name="app_full_name">Anna Hockey League</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_teams">Teams</string>
    <string name="title_activity_players">Players</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <string name="login_email">Enter Email</string>
    <string name="login_password">Enter Password</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="sign_up">New User? Sign Up!</string>
    <string name="forgot">Forgot Password?</string>
    <string name="title_activity_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="title_activity_register">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="title_activity_contacts">Contacts</string>
    <string name="title_activity_sponsors">Sponsors</string>
    <string name="title_activity_history">History</string>
    <string name="title_activity_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="title_activity_results">Fixtures and Results</string>
    <string-array name="image_ids">
        <item>@drawable/chat</item>
        <item>@drawable/play</item>
        <item>@drawable/player</item>
        <item>@drawable/team</item>

    </string-array>
    <string name="RulesContentHeader1">Info</string>
    <string name="RulesContentHeader2">Rules</string>
    <string name="RulesContent1">
           &#8226; The League consists of three levels, each level consisting of 15 matches. \n \n
           &#8226; In each level every team will play five matches. \n \n
    </string>
    <string name="RulesContent2">

           &#8226; The game is equally divided into 5 rounds with the period of 10 minutes each. \n \n
           &#8226; Each team consists of maximum of 9 players on the field including one goal keeper. \n \n
           &#8226; Teams can have any number of bench players under the condition that each player should play at least one round. \n \n
           &#8226; The playing sides will be changed in each round with 2 minutes break and a 4 minute between third and fourth rounds. \n \n
           &#8226; In the 2nd and 3rd rounds team should play with amateur players(first and second year players),
        with maximum of three second year players allowed. Violation will lead to penalty stroke. \n \n
           &#8226; The goal needs to be scored only from the D-circle. \n \n
           &#8226; Own goal won\'t be awarded. \n \n
           &#8226; The ball should be moved 5 yards from any place in taking a foul. \n \n
           &#8226; Hitting the ball is not allowed. \n \n
           &#8226; Sweeping, tapping and slapping the ball is allowed. \n \n
           &#8226; Any appeal to the umpire can be done by the captain only. \n \n
           &#8226; Only three defenders (including goal keeper) and four attackers are allowed in the penalty corner.
        In penalty corner, the defenders need to run from the goal post. \n \n
           &#8226; The ball should be started from the 25 yards line if it crosses the back line. \n \n
           &#8226; The size of the field is 70x50 yards. \n \n
           &#8226; Field umpire decision is final. \n \n
           &#8226; All players should wear proper uniform. \n \n
           &#8226; Points \n \n
               \u0009 <strong><strong><b>Win</b></strong></strong> - 3 points \n \n
                \u0009 <strong><strong><b>Draw</b></strong></strong> - 1 point each \n \n
                \u0009 <strong><strong><b>Lose</b></strong></strong> - 0 points \n \n
            &#8226; Cards \n \n
               \u0009 <strong><font fgcolor="#0f0">Green</font></strong> - Player will be suspended for 2 minutes and substitution is not allowed \n \n
               \u0009 <strong><font fgcolor="#ff0">Yellow</font></strong> - Player will be suspended for 5 minutes and substitution is not allowed \n \n
               \u0009 <strong><font fgcolor="#f00">Red</font></strong> - Player will be dismissed from the current match and substitution will not be allowed \n \n </string>
    <string name="title_activity_rules">Rules</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about">About</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        <strong><b>Anna Hockey League </b></strong>(AHL) is an exclusive tournament in the game of Field Hockey,
        our national game. AHL is conducted by the student players from the constituent
        colleges of Anna University-Chennai i.e. <strong><b>College of Engineering Guindy</b></strong> (CEG),
        <strong><b>Alagappa College of Technology</b></strong> (ACT) and <strong><b>Madras Institute of Technology</b></strong> (MIT) - Chrompet. \n \n

This league is the first of its kind in the history
        of Anna University-Chennai, which is solely conducted by the student players
        of the above mentioned colleges with the perception of drawing interest towards
        our national game as well as to compete themselves to develop their individual skills. \n \n

AHL started it\'s journey from the year (2008)
        and it is planned by the student players that to conduct this AHL every year
        in the even semesters (January to April) to attract more viewers and to create an
        awareness among the students of the Anna University-Chennai campus about the game \'Hockey\'. \n \n

AHL\'08 was inaugurated by former Director of University Sports Board (USB),
        Anna University-Chennai <strong><b>Dr.J.P.Sukumar</b></strong> with the support of all the staffs
        in the University Sports Board. Special interest is being shown on this league
        by the Assistant Physical Directors of USB <strong><b>Dr.B.Balakumaran</b></strong>, <strong><b>Mr.S.Balaganesh</b></strong> and <strong><b>Ms.Evelyn Synthia</b></strong>. \n \n

The funds for conducting the league is being collected from interested organizations and from the alumni players of
        the above mentioned colleges and is handled perfectly by the Mentor <strong><b>Mr.S.Balaganesh</b></strong>
        - Assistant Physical Director, Anna University, Chennai. \n \n

Apart from the regular academic events, the student players involve themselves in
        organizing this league to develop their inter-personal skills,
        leadership skills and also the managerial skills. \n \n
    </string>

</resources>
